Welcome to Booty by Brett, my exclusive
online training program. Each month you
have three options to choose from. The
first option is my favorite, three full
body workouts with two pump days
sandwiched in between. The second
option, four full body days. And the
third option is a 5day lower upper
split, which is very popular amongst the
members. Each of these options come with
different exercises to choose from
depending on your equipment
availability. And members receive their
new program every four weeks. Now, these
workouts are strategically planned and
designed here at Glute Lab, and they're
based on all of my years of experience
as a lifter, as a personal trainer, and
as a scientist and researcher. The
subscription is just $29.95 per month,
so less than a dollar a day. So, if you
want to subscribe, just click on the
button below this video and select
whether you want the monthly or yearly
membership. Now, most of my members stay
subscribed long term, but you can choose
to cancel anytime you want. Immediately
after signing up, you will receive an
activation email. Just follow the
instructions on that email to gain
instant access to the workouts and the
membership benefits. The monthly program
is accompanied by detailed instructional
videos and you also gain access to an
extensive video exercise library. You
also gain access to an exclusive support
group where you can request form checks
from our coaches, ask questions, and get
support from members all over the world.
And I think it's one of a kind. It's the
largest support group of lifters who
were serious about their glute gains. I
didn't design Booty Bubra as a
short-term quick fix program that always
overpromises and underdelivers. I make
sure that you focus on progressive
overload. Each week, you're going to
build upon previous achievements, aiming
to set personal records at the end of
each cycle. Through many years of
extensive testing, we've found that this
is the best possible way to achieve
long- lasting, consistent results. So,
join Booty Barrett today. Start the
program now and start seeing real
results.
[Music]